[
    {
        "title" : " Militaries"
    },


    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
      "answer": "China"
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
        "answer": "India"
    },

    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
        "answer": "USA"
      },
      {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
          "answer": "North Korea"
      },

    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
        "answer": "Russia"
      },
      {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
          "answer": "Ukraine"
      },

    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
        "answer": "Pakistan"
      },
      {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
          "answer": "Iran"
      },

    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
        "answer": "Ethiopia"
      },
      {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "What are the Largest Active Militries in the world according to the International Institute for Strategic Studies",
          "answer": "South Korea"
      }
]
  